Episode 58
Tokyo No. 1 Colony, Part 5
Domain Expansion:
Chimera Shadow Garden.
Esoteric Technique: Hollow Wicker Basket!
Hollow Wicker Basket is the origin of
New Shadow Style's "Simple Domain."
It possesses the ability
to neutralize a domain
and counter its guaranteed-hit factor.
Too bad!
The "Domain Amplification" used
by Jogo and Hanami in Shibuya
utilized a domain capable of harboring
a guaranteed-hit,
guaranteed-kill technique...
Why is it hitting me?!
...and intentionally left out
their cursed techniques
to leave space for Gojo's
cursed technique to flow into,
neutralizing his Limitless.
However, Hollow Wicker
Basket and Simple Domain
aren't capable of neutralizing
the cursed technique.
They work by neutralizing a barrier
imbued with a cursed technique
to nullify the imbued technique's
guaranteed-hit effect.
However, Fushiguro's
domain is incomplete.
You're not sneering anymore.
Damn brat!
By transposing his domain onto
the space of the gymnasium,
he managed to force it to close,
but it's not imbued with a
guaranteed-hit technique.
Don't act like you've won!
Now I see.
Chimera Shadow Garden
currently just extends his
Ten Shadows Technique,
and draws out 120% of
his latent potential.
However, that very imperfection
is what caught Reggie Star off-guard.
Both his clones and his shikigami had
physical forms before striking me.
That means this barrier
isn't imbued with a
guaranteed-hit technique!
The domain's buff to his technique's
abilities is no joke, though.
This is even worse to deal with than
a simple guaranteed-hit domain!
If he pulls out that elephant
here and drenches me in water,
it'll halve my options,
and I'll probably lose.
But...
it's so like me
to make sure that won't happen.
Nue!
Too slow!
I knew it.
For a while now,
I've had to reinforce my footing with
cursed energy to avoid getting sucked in.
The whole bottom of this domain
is your shadow, right?
Being able to store and remove yourself
and objects is convenient, isn't it?
But one thing nagged at me.
"He doesn't have many weapons."
I've only seen you use
one paltry cursed tool.
Either it has a low capacity
and you need to reserve space
for yourself at all times,
or you're forced to bear the weight of
things stored in your shadow yourself.
Looks like the latter was spot-on!
Now I've turned the design
of your domain against you.
With three passenger cars,
your current weight is 2.4 tons.
Looks like your clones weren't
able to tolerate it,
but can you still produce your shikigami?
Either way, I'll just
need to mind my footing
as I keep adding weight until
you're crushed under it.
Are you stupid?
Huh?
Even if it's incomplete,
a domain is still a domain!
My shadow's above us, too!
Which of us will get crushed first,
Reggie?!
JUJUTSU KAISEN
The Culling Game Part 1
It's said that a typical human will
lose consciousness at five to six Gs.
2.4 tons.
As Fushiguro weighed 60 kilograms,
that meant he was currently
suffering 40 Gs.
In order to prevent his blood from
pooling in his legs from the high Gs
and depriving his brain of blood flow,
Fushiguro was lowering his posture
and reinforcing his body
with cursed energy,
paying special attention to his legs.
A mature African elephant
weighs three to six tons.
With the domain's improvement
to his technique's accuracy,
Max Elephant accurately
recreated its real weight.
Under that weight, Reggie Star's right
fibula and heel bone were cracked.
Both of them faced
the possibility of being crushed
to death at any second.
I screwed up!
I could have won if I'd kept
the trucks in reserve!
What do I do?
I got splashed with some
water at the same time,
but my trump card's still safe.
I could slip into his shadow and
recreate my trump card inside it.
That would crush him!
No...
If he's not dismissing his domain,
that means anything in his shadow is
stuck there after he dismisses his domain!
What if I'm stuck in his shadow
forever after he dies?
What's it like inside his shadow, anyway?
It looks like a liquid,
but can I breathe in it?
Can I float?
No. Submerging into his
shadow is too risky.
So while stuck in this state...
I have to pull out my trump
card and activate it!
Contractual Re-Creation!
Snap
I didn't make it in time!
And there's no air inside his shadow!
No buoyancy or resistance, either!
I'm just... sinking!
My consciousness... is fading...
Not yet! Endure it a little longer!
Wait until I'm sure he's dead
before dismissing the domain!
Then I can expel what's in my shadow!
The things I recreate
disappear soon after carrying
out the command I give them.
I hadn't given the cars
I sank a command, though.
I didn't want them
disappearing, after all.
That meant I could still
issue them a command.
"Take me and rise up!"
The weight of one car is gone
now, but that saved my life.
I'll admit it.
You're strong.
But I'm stronger!
Contractual Re-Creation!
A 132-square-foot,
two-story wooden frame structure!
The framework alone weighs
at least thirty tons!
Get crushed!
What happened?!
Did I fall into his shadow again?
No!
I'm in actual water!
How?!
It's heavy!
Is that brat trying to strangle me?
What power!
No, that's wrong!
It's from the weight of
the two cars I added!
This is bad!
This time, I'm sinking!
I have to dismiss
Contractual Re-Creation!
Right!
This is a community gymnasium!
And the gymnasium's basement
is a heated swimming pool!
Did he flee into his shadow
and dismiss his domain,
forcing me to destroy the floor
and plunge into the pool?
You can't use your receipts when
they're that soaked, can you?
He waited instead of
pursuing me immediately.
He let his technique recover after
exhausting it with his domain, then?
Are you sure about that?
I'm betting you can't produce
shikigami anymore either, right?
That's true.
You do understand what
comes next, don't you?
He'll use a shikigami other than that dog.
But none of them can
deal a decisive blow.
So use it!
The moment you let up,
I'll finish you with a counter!
Demon Dogs isn't weak enough
to let that stop it.
Sorcerers are all liars, huh?
JUJUTSU KAISEN
The domain,
the pool...
All to convince me you couldn't
use that dog anymore.
You didn't flee into this gymnasium.
You lured me into it.
To think I'd let a modern sorcerer,
and a brat at that, get the better of me.
Even if I wanted to flee, Nue can't
fly with someone for very long.
I've struggled with that before.
What's your relation to Tengen-sama?
Tengen?
Oh, right.
They would still be alive, huh?
That shut-in.
Yeah? That's enough.
Reggie said Tengen-sama's claims about
the Culling Game's goals were a bluff.
I should probably consider
the possibility that
Tengen-sama and Kenjaku are secretly
connected and lied about their goal,
but that doesn't seem
likely from his reaction.
Kogane, give him all my points.
Okay!
You have received
41 points from Reggie Star.
What are you plotting?
That's an awful thing to say.
It's my good deed before I die.
I'm just a spectator.
I was never close friends with Kenjaku.
I think doing this will
make things interesting.
That's my intuition.
Please.
You did kill me, after all.
Let fate toy with you
a bit, and die a fool.
You have gained five points.
Did I get him?!
No! Don't let your guard down!
He's tough!
What the hell?!
Slide
Why are you covered in lotion?!
It could be sauce.
Shut up! Die!
Wait, it really is sauce?!
Damn it!
Seriously, what's with this guy?!
I've blown him up several times!
I feel like I've killed him five times!
So how does he have so little damage?!
So little.
You hate sauce?
His first injury healed
at some point, too.
But he hasn't shown any signs of using
reverse cursed techniques like I do.
I don't get it!
Hazenoki-sama.
What?
Reggie Star-sama has just died.
Oh? What happened?
I'm going home.
I'm sick of this.
Okay!
Take a bath!
And brush your teeth!
Hey, man! Give me your points!
Stop following me.
Please! Just think of it
as going with the flow!
Die.
Takaba's cursed technique, Comedian,
makes whatever he's convinced
would be funny a reality.
It's a technique capable of
opposing even Satoru Gojo.
Yet Takaba doesn't know anything
about his own technique.
I don't get it! I don't get it!
Ever since I became an adult,
I hardly understand anything!
I've heard that all men are wolves,
but it's always those wolves who take
care of the confusing stuff for me!
If those wolves will handle everything,
then I don't need to
think about anything!
Because I'm so cute!
Those wolves always... always...
Don't, Megumi.
You'll spare me?
Shut up.
Damn sister.
Events progressed quickly
in the Sendai Colony,
Sendai City, Miyagi Prefecture, November 12th, 11:28
far outstripping those
of the Tokyo Colony
and becoming especially fierce.
Dhruv Lakdawalla. Current points: 91.
This is his second incarnation.
He's an old man who
single-handedly conquered
this archipelago during
the Civil War of Wa.
He possesses two autonomous shikigami,
and the orbit of those shikigami
determines his domain.
Ryu Ishigori. Current points: 77.
He's the cannon with the greatest
cursed energy output among the Players.
Takako Uro. Current points: 70.
She was originally the captain of
the Sun, Moon, and Stars Squad,
a squad of assassins serving
directly under the Fujiwara Clan.
She possesses a technique that
allows her to manipulate "the sky."
Kurourushi. Current points: 54.
It's a cockroach cursed
spirit that Kenjaku freed
from the control of cursed
spirit manipulation.
It ranks as a special-grade
(already registered).
It's currently lying dormant until
certain conditions are met.
There was no alliance between them,
but their complex compatibility
and opposing strength
led them into a three—no,
a four-way stalemate.
But one of those pillars
has fallen.
Yuta Okkotsu. Current points: 35.
Three months after the
Night Parade of a Hundred Demons,
he had blossomed as a
special-grade sorcerer.
He was a modern sorcerer
rivaling Satoru Gojo
in unusual abilities.
I'll obtain 400 points on my own.
Yuta, which would you like?
It's called Kurourushi!
Give me everything.
Give me back Yuta!
Sensei, I won't let you kill
your best friend twice.
Next Episode
Sendai Colony